Guide to the Talmage Farlow Documentary Film Collection, 1979-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Talmage Farlow Documentary Film collection 1979-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
DeStefano, Lorenzo
77 linear feet Extent: circa 8000 Items
Filmmaker Lorenzo DeStefano directed and produced a documentary on jazz guitarist Talmage Farlow (1921-1998) titled Talmage Farlow (Productions A-Propos, 1981). The collection contains audio, moving image, and paper materials created and compiled by DeStefano during the production and distribution of the documentary and its related audio recordings.
RL.00381
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, all original audio and moving image materials are closed to patron use. Unless otherwise noted below, CD or DVD use copies must be made for access to content.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Talmage Farlow Documentary Film Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in December 2010.
Biographical Note
Filmmaker Lorenzo DeStefano directed and produced a documentary on jazz guitarist Talmage Farlow (1921-1998) titled Talmage Farlow (Productions A-Propos, 1981). Farlow, born in Greensboro, NC, achieved professional musical success beginning in the 1940s, performing in bands led by Marjorie Hyams, Red Norvo, Artie Shaw, and others. Farlow also began leading his own bands in the 1950s. In 1958, Farlow removed himself from full-time performing and relocated to Sea Bright, NJ, where he worked as a sign painter while teaching occasional guitar lessons and performing at local venues. By the late 1970s, he began performing more broadly, including a reunion with Red Norvo and concert tours throughout the USA and Europe. He passed away in 1998 due to complications from esophageal cancer.
Collection Overview
The Talmage Farlow Documentary Film Collection consists of materials created and compiled by filmmaker Lorenzo DeStefano during the making of the film Talmage Farlow and several related audio recordings. The majority of the materials are in various audio and moving image formats, including 16mm and 35mm film, Hi8, Betacam SP, VHS, DVD, 1/4 inch and 1/2 inch open reel audio tape, audiocassette, and CD. These are located in the Audio and Moving Image Materials Series. The Paper Files Series includes materials maintained by DeStefano on the production, distribution, and marketing of the documentary and its related audio recordings.
Subject Headings
16mm; 35mm; Audiocassettes; Audiotapes; Betacam-SP; Color film (film); Compact discs; DeStefano, Lorenzo; Documentary films; Documentary films -- Production and direction; Documentary films -- United States -- Distribution; DVDs; Farlow, Tal; Guitarists -- United States -- Biography; Hi-8.; Jazz musicians -- United States -- Biography; Photographs; Videocassettes
Detailed Description of Collection
- Audio and Moving Image Materials, 1980-2006 and undated, (45 boxes)
  Audio and moving image materials created or acquired by Lorenzo DeStefano during the research for and making of the Tal Farlow documentary film and its related audio recordings. The majority of the moving image materials are 16mm and 35mm film, and the majority of the audio materials are 1/4 inch and 1/2 inch tape. Other formats include Betacam SP, Hi8, VHS, DVD, audiocassette, and CD. Original titles have been maintained.
  Many items required extensive cleaning and mold remediation during their initial processing, which necessitated discarding original boxes and reels. Those items are identified below with the file name JAD-2010-0179-[item number]. All original titles from the boxes and reels have been transcribed and maintained below.
  RESTRICTIONS: All original analog audio and moving image materials are CLOSED to patron use. Unless otherwise noted, CD or DVD use copies must be made for access to content.
  - 16mm original neg.; 62-13-14-15 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 62-12-13 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 67-28-29-30 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 70 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 73-23-24-25-26 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 73-26-27 (Box 1)
  - 16mm original neg.; 62-19-20-21 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 62-40-41 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 62-42-43-44 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 67-26-27-28 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 03-79-80-81 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 04-85-86 (Box 2)
  - 16mm original neg.; 05-85-86 (Box 3)
  - 16mm original neg.; 07-30-31-32 (Box 3)
  - 16mm original neg.; 07-67-68-69 (Box 3)
  - 16mm original neg.; 22-68-69-70-71-72 (Box 3)
  - 16mm original neg.; 23-39-40-41-42 (Box 3)
  - 16mm; Talmage Farlow Dream (2x) (Box 3)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F001; MX Dupe; R4, R5, R6 (Box 4)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F002; miscellaneous film elements (Box 4)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F003; miscellaneous film elements (Box 4)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F004; miscellaneous film elements (Box 4)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F005; miscellaneous film elements (Box 4)
  - 16mm original neg.; 27-96-97 (Box 5)
  - 16mm original neg.; 27-95-96 (Box 5)
  - 16mm original neg.; 35-76-77 (Box 5)
  - 16mm original neg.; 41-07-08-09-10 (Box 5)
  - 16mm original neg.; C42-22 (Box 5)
  - 16mm original neg.; 23-42-43 (Box 5)
  - 16mm; Foot B, Title IP, Hi-Cons for Supers - Interviews; Foot A, Interview BG's for Supers; Foot C, Roll IP, Red Mitchell BG only (Box 6)
  - 16mm; A Roll ECO, D-31941; new Jimmy Lyon Footage (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333056; 7247 (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333054; 7247; 8/9/80 (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333057; 7247; 8/9/80 (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333044; 7247; 8/9/80 (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333058; 7247; 8/9/80 (Box 6)
  - 16mm Normal Work Print; 333066; 7247; 8/9/80 (Box 6)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-025; 11/6/80; Tal U.O. (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-026; Clean 10/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-027; Sndtrk Selections; Fasc. Rhythm, I Hear a Rhapsody, I Love You, Cherokee (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-028; Mono SR 2B; Public Theatre; 8/9/80; Radio mic mix (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-029; Mono SR 3B; Public Theatre; 8/9/80; Radio mikes, applause (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-030; Mono SR 4B; Public Theatre; 8/9/80; Radio mikes, applause (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR8, Original Master; Sign of the Times, 5/21/80; Tal/Lenny Breau (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR9, Original Master; Sign of the Times, 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR10, Original Master; Sign of the Times, 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR11, Original Master; Sign of the Times, 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R11, Safety Copy; Sign of the Times, 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-1; Penthouse, Wireless; 5/14/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-13; Neighbors (end), Lenny's walk; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-14; Tal/Lenny Int; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-15; Tal/Lenny Int (cont); 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-16; Tal/Lenny Porch; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-17; Tal/Lenny Porch (cont); 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-18; Tal/Lenny Porch (end); 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-19; Lenny walk #2, Tal Flag pole, Tal int #2; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-20; Tal int #2 (end), Tal int #3, Tal Fishing; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-21; Wild Evening Dock, Neighbors #2; 5/20/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-22; Tina Interview; 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-23; Tina Interview (cont); 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SRM-24; Tina Interview (end); 5/21/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 7A; Art D'Lugoff Interview; 8/10/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 6A; Public Theatre; CR A8, A11, B13; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 5A; Public Theatre; CR B3, A3, B4, A8; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 4A; Public Theatre; CR B2, B3, A2; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 3A; Public Theatre; CR C1, B2; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 2A; Public Theatre; CR A2, A1; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 1A; Public Theatre; CR B1, A1; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR 1B; Public Theatre Lobby; 8/9/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; L/S Norvo; Reel #1; March, 28, 81 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; L/S Norvo; Reel #2; March, 28, 81 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; L/S Norvo; Reel #3; March, 28, 81 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; L/S Farlow; Reel #4; March, 28, 81 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; L/S Benson; Reel #5; March, 28, 81 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R1; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, NJ; 10/5/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R3; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, NJ; 10/5/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R4; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, NJ; 10/5/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R5; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, NJ; 10/5/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio; R5; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, NJ; 10/5/80 (Box 7)
  - 1/4 inch audio Music Lesson (cont), 5/21/80 SRM-25 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal Interview, Sea Bright, 10/5/80; R-2 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal NYU #1; 6/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal NYU #2; 6/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal NYU #3; 6/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-031; SR S-3 14 May 1980; Penthouse Session (NJPTV #33); Stereo 1/4 2 Track; Fasc Rythmn Tk 1/2; Jam; Impromptu Tal Solo (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-032; SR S-4 14 May 1980; Penthouse Session (NJPTV #33); Fact Rythmn Tk 3/4; Rhapsody Tk 1 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-033; R-2 1/4 2 Track Stereo; Public Theatre (8/9/80); Fasc. Rhythm, Longhorn Blues, Green Dolphin St., Cowhand, Autumn in NY (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-034; R-3 2-track 1/4 Stereo Master; Public Theatre (8/9/80); Concert; Smooth as the Wind, My Foolish Heart, Blues (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-001; SR M-5; 5/15/80; A. Murray (cont) (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-002; SR M-4; 5/14/80-5/15/80; Penthouse Control; A. Murray (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-003; SR M-7; 5/15/80; J. Lyon (cont) (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-004; 11/30/80; NYC #3; S-6 Room Tone (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-005; 11/6/80; Sea Bright (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-006; Tal Autumn in MY vintage (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-007; SR 9/9/80; NY Wild; Streets, Voices, Hycrant (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-008; SR M-2; Penthouse Wireless; 5/14/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-009; SR M-3; Penthouse Wireless; 5/14/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-010; SR M-6; J. Lyon; 5/15/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-011; SR M-8; Signwrk, Wild Snd, Signwrk; 5/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-012; SR M-9; Singwrd, Boatyand; 5/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-013; 11/30/80; NYC Wild FX #1 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-014; 11/30/80; NYC Bechet's #2 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-015; SR M-10; Wild Tal Boatyand; Tal Int 1 (nite); 5/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-016; SR M-11; Tal Int 1 (cont); 5/19/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-017; SR M-12; Tal Int 1 (end); Neighbors; 5/19/80, 5/20 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-018; Wild Sea Bright; 11/6/80; Fishermen, Puck Puck, Air, Brief Tal V.O. (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-019; Tal Pre-shoot Interviews (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-020; Tal R3 5/10/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-021; Tal R2 5/10/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-022; Tal R5 5/10/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-023; Tal R1 5/10/80 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio: JAD-2010-0179-024; 12/1/80; Lorenzo's Off Camera Lines; Close Mic and Off Mic; Master 7 1/2 ips (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign of the Times - w/ Lenny B; R-8 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign of the Times - w/ Lenny B; R-9 (Box 8)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign of the Times - w/ Lenny B; R-10 (Box 8)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Tal Farlow Concert; Tape 4 copy (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Tal Farlow Concert; Tape 3 copy (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Tal Farlow Concert; Tape 2 copy (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Tal Farlow Concert; Tape 1 copy (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Penthouse Session; R-3 (continued from R-2) (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Penthouse Session; R-2 (continued from R-1, beginning R-2) (Box 9)
  - 1/2 inch audio; Penthouse Session; R-1 (Box 9)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign of the Times - w/ Trio; R-6 (Box 9)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal Farlow R-7, Sign of the Times; 2 trk Stereo; 15 ips (Box 10)
  - 1/2 inch audio, 4-trk, 15 ips; Tal Farlow, 8-9-80 Concert; Tape 1 (Box 10)
  - 1/2 inch audio, 4-trk, 15 ips; Tal Farlow, 8-9-80 Concert; Tape 2 (Box 10)
  - 1/2 inch audio, 4-trk, 15 ips; Tal Farlow, 8-9-80 Concert; Tape 3 (Box 10)
  - 1/2 inch audio, 4-trk, 15 ips; Tal Farlow, 8-9-80 Concert; Tape 4 (Box 10)
  - 1/4 inch audio, 2 track stereo; Public Theatre; R-1 (Box 10)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Penthouse 5/14/80; 4 trk, 1 of 2 (Box 10)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Penthouse 5/14/80; 4 trk, 2 of 2 (Box 10)
  - 16mm neg, 65116; A and B rolls; Talmage Farlow R2 (Box 11)
  - 16mm orig neg, 64414; for Title BG interviews; Talmage Farlow 1G (Box 11)
  - 16 mm B-Wind, 65115; opt trk; Talmage Farlow R-2 (Box 11)
  - 16mm IP, 76466; Talmage Farlow R-1 (Box 11)
  - 16mm A-Wind IP, 76467; Talmage Farlow R-2 (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal Farlow Roll S-1, Tommy's Apt; 5/13/80; 7 1/2 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Tal Farlow Roll S-2, Tommy's Apt; 5/13/80; 7 1/2 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign, 5/21/80, S-6; 15 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sign, 5/21/80, S-7; 15 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Dilts mix-down 11/24/80; Remixed 1/19/81 (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; SR S-5; Tal plays alone at home, 5/18/80; 7 1/2 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Sound Track #1, 11/80; 7 1/2 ips (Box 11)
  - 1/4 inch audio; Dilts mix, old, noisy; 7 1/2 ips (Box 11)
  - [Miscellaneous visual slides along with DAT, audiocassette, and Hi8 recordings generated during the making of the documentary.] (Box 12)
  - 16mm; Tal V/O, c#1 (Box 13)
  - 16mm; Tal V/O, c#2 and 3 (Box 13)
  - 16mm; Wild Sound, Tal V/O (Box 13)
  - 16mm; Public, R-4B wireless (Box 13)
  - 16mm; 11/30/80 NYC and Sea Brite; Wild Sound (Box 13)
  - 35mm; Temp Mix #3, R-1, R-2 (Box 13)
  - 35mm; Penthouse, Jam 1 and 2; M Trk (Box 13)
  - 35mm; 06/15/81; Talmage Farlow R-6 (Box 13)
  - 35mm MX Trims; Tal Farlow, R-2 (Box 13)
  - 16mm comp copy; R's 4, 5, 6; 6-16-81 (Box 14)
  - 16mm comp copy; R's 1, 2, 3; 6-16-81 (Box 14)
  - 35mm; 6-12-81; R-1 (Box 14)
  - 35mm; 6-12-81; R-2 (Box 14)
  - 35mm; 6-15-81; R-3 (Box 14)
  - 35mm; 6-15-81; R-4 (Box 14)
  - 35mm; 6-15-81; R-5 (Box 14)
  - 16mm; Penthouse, Rhapsody; B and C cam, Tks 1 and 2; EA 0000-1042 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Penthouse, Rhapsody; A cam, Tks 1 and 2, Trims; EA, EB, EC 0000-1042 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Control Room; A 0000-1004; FA 0000-1107 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Tommy's Apt, Trio Rehearsals; R-4 of 4; BB 4200-5640 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Tommy's Apt, Trio Rehearsals; R-1 of 4; BB 0000-1708 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Talmage Farlow R1, A and B Roll; 6/21/83 (Box 15)
  - 16mm; Concert, Longhorn Blues; PX and TRK; R-8; BP, BQ 7000, BR 7450, BS (Box 16)
  - 16mm; Concert, I'm an Old Cowhand; PX and TRK; R-10; BQ, BR 9000, BS 9700, BT (Box 16)
  - 16mm; Concert, Green Dolphin Street; PX and TRK, Box 1 of 2; R-9; BQ 8000-8950 (Box 16)
  - 16mm; Concert, Green Dolphin Street; PX C/D, Box 2 of 2; R-9; BR 8000, BS 8950 (Box 16)
  - 16mm; Concert, Stardust; PX and TRK; R-6; BP, BQ 5000, BR 5650, BS (Box 17)
  - 16mm; Concert, Fascinating Rhythm; PX and TRK; R-7; BP, BQ 6000, BR 6750, BS (Box 17)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre, Misc MDS; BK 4000, 5900 (Box 17)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre, Pre-concert, Lighting Change; BK 8700-9905 (Box 17)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Tal Solos, #1 and 2, A Cam only; PX and TRK; CA 0000-0814 (Box 18)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Fasc Rhythm, TK 3, A Cam only; PX and TRK; DA 0000-0817 (Box 18)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Fasc Rhythm, TKS 1 and 2, A Cam only; PX and TRK; AA 0000-1193 (Box 18)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Fasc Rhythm, #1 and 2, B Cam only; PX and TRK; AB 0000-1193 (Box 18)
  - 16mm; Penthouse; Fasc Rhythm, #1 and 2, C Cam only; PX; AC 0000-1193 (Box 18)
  - 16mm; Concert: Tuning, Donna Lee; PX and TRK; R-1, Box 1 of 2; BP 0000, BQ 0975 (Box 19)
  - 16mm; Concert: MOS; Trims; BU 5000-5275 (Box 19)
  - 16mm; Concert: Smooth as the Wind; PX and TRK; R-12, Trims; BU, BV 1000, BW 1450, BX (Box 19)
  - 16mm; Concert: My Foolish Heart; PX and TRK; R-13; BU, BV 2000, BW 2375, BX (Box 19)
  - 16mm; Concert: Autumn in New York; PX and TRK; R-11; BU, BV 0000, BW 0675, BX, BY (Box 19)
  - 16mm; Concert: Posthorn Blues; PX and TRK; R-14; BU, BV, BW 3000, BX 4500, BY (Box 20)
  - 16mm; Concert: Jordu; Box 1 of 2, PX and TRK; R-3; BP 2000, BQ 2750 (Box 20)
  - 16mm; Concert: Jordu; Box 2 of 2, PX C/D; R-3; BR 2000, BS 2750 (Box 20)
  - 16mm; Concert: Flamingo; PX and TRK; R-2, Trims; BP 1000, BQ 1515, BS (Box 20)
  - 16mm; Tommy's Apt, Trio Rehearsal; R-2 of 4; PX and TRK; BB 2000-2950 (Box 21)
  - 16mm; Penthouse, Jam #1-2; A Cam; PX and TRK; BA 0000 (Box 21)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre: Preconcert Setup and Rehearsal; PX-1; BK 6000 (Box 21)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre: Preconcert Setup and Rehearsal; 2nd cam coverage; culled 11/18/80 (Box 21)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre: Preconcert Setup and Rehearsal; Slates 1-8, 16, 17, 20-26 (Box 21)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F006; miscellaneous film elements (Box 22)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F007; Bechet's, 11/30/80, PX and TRK (Box 22)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F008; Wild: NYC FX (SR 9/9/80), uncoded (Box 22)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F009; George Benson Int. (Box 22)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F010; N.Y.C. scenes, no codes+C222 (Box 22)
  - 16mm; Red Norvo, Wild; J 1000-3318 (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Penthouse, Rhapsody, TKS 1 and 2; M-TRK, Uncoded (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Pulled, VO's; TRK (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Montage Music; TRK (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Misc BG Fill; TRK (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Tina's Int Lines (for poss addtl int matl); (w/ transcript) (Box 23)
  - 16mm; Outs: Trailer Sections (Box 24)
  - 16mm; Loops (Box 24)
  - 16mm; Interview Titles, Misc NG's (Box 24)
  - 16mm; R3; WK MX 1, WK MX 2, A Dial (Box 24)
  - 16mm; Talmage Farlow Trailer #2, 12 mins (Box 24)
  - 16mm; Talmage Farlow Trailer #3, 12 mins (Box 24)
  - 16mm; R-6, Backup FX 1 and 2 (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-4, WK MX 1, WK MX 2, A Dial (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-4, FX 1, FX 2, B Dial (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-3, FX 1, FX 2, B Dial (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-1, FX 1, FX 2, FX 3 (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-6, Work MX, 1/2 (Box 25)
  - 16mm; R-2, FX1, FX2, FX3 (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-2, A Dial, B Dial, WK MX 1, WK MX 2 (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-1, Work Mix 1, Work Mix 2 (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-1, A Dial, B Dial (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-5, A Dial, FX1, FX2 (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-5, WK MX 1, WK MX 2 (Box 26)
  - 16mm; R-5, FX2, FX3, FX4 (Box 27)
  - 16mm; Lenny Walks, Tal/Lenny Int; D98842 (Box 27)
  - 16mm; Tal/Lenny Porch; D98804 (Box 27)
  - 16mm; Tal/Lenny, Sign of Times, R1; D98733 (Box 27)
  - 16mm; Tal/Lenny, Sign of Times, R2; D98804 (Box 27)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F011; Concert, Papp intro, tuning, Donna Lee, PX C/D, Box 2 of 2, (R-1), Sync cut (Box 28)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F012_1; Concert, Angel Eyes, PX and TRK, (R-4) (Box 28)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F012_2; miscellaneous film elements (Box 28)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F013; miscellaneous film elements (Box 28)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F014; miscellaneous film elements (Box 28)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F015; miscellaneous film elements (Box 29)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F016; miscellaneous film elements (Box 29)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F017; miscellaneous film elements (Box 29)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F018; miscellaneous film elements (Box 29)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F019; miscellaneous film elements (Box 29)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F020; miscellaneous film elements (Box 30)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F021; miscellaneous film elements (Box 30)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F022; miscellaneous film elements (Box 30)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F023; miscellaneous film elements (Box 30)
  - 16mm; JAD-2010-0179-F024; miscellaneous film elements (Box 30)
  - 16mm original neg; 96-43-44-45 (Box 31)
  - 16mm original neg; End Credits, BG's (Box 31)
  - 16mm; New W/P, BG's with Super T; New 8/21 (Box 31)
  - 16mm interneg; BG's Interviews w/ Supers; New 8/12/81 (Box 31)
  - 16mm; Old A/B IP Roll; Titled BG's (Box 31)
  - 16mm; [untitled] (Box 31)
  - 16mm; Misc Optical Elements (Box 32)
  - 16mm original neg; Interview Scenes, BG Scenes, IP Trims (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre Concert; R-5, A Cam (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre Concert; R-5, B Cam (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre Concert; R-5, C Cam (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre Concert; R-5, D Cam (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre Concert; R-5, Work Track; BP 4000 (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Mixing Reel 2 (MX Dupe) (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Mixing Reel 3 (MX Dupe) (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Mixing R1 (MX Dupe) (Box 32)
  - 16mm; Wild Sound, 5/80 Shoot; W0700-3965, BF0250-0842, W0300-0634 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; Public Theatre; Wild, Pre-Concert; W4000-5475 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; SC 4A Trims; BC2500-7800 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; SC 4A Practice; R2 of 4, PX and TRK; BC 4000-5885 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; SC 4A Practice; R3 of 4, PX and TRK; BC 6000-6800 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; SC 4A Practice; R4 of 4, MOS; BC 7000-7800 (Box 33)
  - 16mm; Color Work Print, R1-2 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Sea Bright Scenes; R1-2; BD0000-1350, 1500-2760 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Tommy's Apt, Trio Rehearsals; R3 of 4, PX and TRK; BB 3000-4000 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Tina Interview, PX and TRK; BH 0000-2750 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Concert, Wild Snd; W 6000-7575 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Penthouse, Fasc Rhythm, TK 4; A Cam Only, PX and TRK; DA 0818-1183 (Box 34)
  - 16mm; Music Lesson, PX and TRK; BH 3000-4275 (Box 35)
  - 16mm; Albert Murray Int, Lifts/Outs (Box 35)
  - 16mm; SC 4A, Practice; R1 of 4, PX and TRK; BC 2500-3615 (Box 35)
  - 16mm; Tal Interview #2 (Day Int); BG 5000-6825 (Box 35)
  - 16mm; Tal Interview #3 (Dock); BG 7000-7465 (Box 35)
  - 35mm; R1, B Wind (Box 35)
  - 16mm; Sign Work on Dock; R1 and 2, PX and TRK; BF 0000-1300, 1500-2150 (Box 36)
  - 16mm; Tal Fishing (and Jack Litch #2); PX and TRK; BG 7600-8350 (Box 36)
  - 16mm; Boatyard, PX and TRK; BF 2500-3465 (Box 36)
  - 16mm; Tal Int #1 (Nite); PX and TRK; BF 4000-6675 (Box 36)
  - 16mm; Neighbor, PX and TRK; BF 6800-8525 (Box 36)
  - 16mm neg; R1, B Wind (Box 37)
  - 16mm neg; R2, B Wind (Box 37)
  - 16mm; 11/20 Temp Mix, R1 Assembly (Box 37)
  - 16mm; 11/20 Temp Mix 1, Concert Seq (Box 37)
  - 16mm; 12/3/80 Temp Mix #2, R1 (Box 37)
  - 16mm; 12/3/80 Temp Mix #2, R2 (Box 37)
  - 16mm, finished film; R1, R2 (Box 38)
  - 16mm; Track 2B, 3B; Joe Papp, Uncoded (Box 38)
  - 16mm; Misc Trims (Box 39)
  - 16mm; Red Norvo Int; BB 1000-4318 (Box 39)
  - 16mm; Stereo Music Master; 11-8-89 (Box 40)
  - 16mm; Stereo Music Copy (Box 40)
  - 16mm; Stereo Copy; 7-7-86 (Box 40)
  - 16mm; Misc Trims (Box 41)
  - 16mm; Misc Trims (Box 41)
  - Finished Film; 3/4 inch Preview Copy (8 copies) (Box 42)
  - Finished Film; 3/4 inch Stereo Master (Box 42)
  - Finished Film; 3/4 inch Master Copy (Box 42)